{
  "vocabulary":[
     {
        "question":"Tan Tan(talk about)",
        "answer":"谈谈"
     },
     {
        "question":"Jue 定(decide)",
        "answer":"决定"
     },
     {
        "question":"Xu 要(have to)",
        "answer":"需要"
     },
     {
        "question":"想去na,就去na",
        "answer":"哪"
     },
     {
        "question":"dan心(worry about)",
        "answer":"担心"
     },
     {
        "question":"shu服(comfortable)",
        "answer":"舒服"
     },
     {
        "question":"fang间",
        "answer":"房间"
     },
     {
        "question":"chuang(Bed)",
        "answer":"床"
     },
     {
        "question":"jiandan(simple)",
        "answer":"简单"
     },
     {
        "question":"huan xi yi fu (change clothes)",
        "answer":"换洗衣服"
     },
     {
        "question":"玩ju(toy)",
        "answer":"玩具"
     }
  ]
}